Madeline Jensen

Senior developer with over 8 years of experience in web development, strategy, and leadership. My experience includes managing the planning, design, and development for many projects from concept to implementation.

Ariel, WA - Remote (360) 431-1979 madelinelise@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Mediacurrent — Senior Developer

July 2019 - PRESENT

- Manage the planning and development of web applications from design to completion.
- Continuously work to improve user experience and accessibility for client projects.
- Involved in mentorship programs to help our team grow.

Volusia County Schools — Supervisor, Web Services

Dec 2016 - July 2019

- Led the Web Services team that was responsible for managing around 70 school sites.
- Planned and led the redesign of district and school websites.

Furniture Leisure — Manager, Web Content

Dec 2014 - Dec 2016

- Oversaw the relaunch of 2 eCommerce websites to an upgraded system, new design, and revamped content for SEO.
- Worked collaboratively with the sales and development team to optimize the user experience and search engine rankings, resulting in a \$2M increase in revenue during my 2-year tenure.

SKILLS

React

Javascript

SASS/SCSS

HTML5

GraphQL

Gatsby

PHP

Twig

Flexbox & Grid

Drupal 7/8/9

Pattern Lab / Storybook

Node/npm/nvm

Git

Photoshop

Sketch

Design Systems

E2E & Unit Testing

Mentorship Programs

Sprint Planning

Managing Releases

EDUCATION

Daytona State College — Bachelor's of Science - Information Technology

Graduated 2017

PROJECTS

See https://madelineiensen.netlifv.app/